#### **Career Summary**

Electronic engineer with +5 years of experience as Frontend developer, Knowledge of HTML, CSS, Javascript: libraires/frameworks such JOuery, Bootstrap, Angular2+/AngularJS, React/React-Native; agile methodology SCRUM; version control Git + sourcetree; CMS: eZPublish, Wordpress, Joomla. Felipe has worked with projects both locally and internationally.

#### Summary of Qualifications

Skills:

HTML Angular CSS/Sass 2+/AngularJ

Javascript

JQuery React/React-Native

S

Bootstrap

Git

Sourcetree

Scrum methodology

Responsive

Languages

Spanish (native speaker)

English (advanced)

#### Career History

# Freelance, Bogotá, Colombia

Frontend Developer

Oct 2021 -

- Bringing support with a logistic company based in the U.S to migrate legacy web Apps to latest Web technologies.
- Technologies/Languages: React, TypeScript, React Material, StoryBook, HTML, CSS, Javascript, scss, REDUX Toolkit

#### Globant, Bogotá, Colombia

Web UI Developer

Aug. 2018 - Sept 2021

TypeScript

- Be part of an international Team to deliver solutions to different clients/companies based in U.S.
- Technologies/Languages: React JS, Mobx, GIT, E2E test, Unit testing, React Testing Library, Jest, Cypress, Typescript, responsive design, Angular 8, Typescript, responsive design, GIT, MapKit JS, unit testing, React Native, Redux, saas, Bootstrap, Cucumber BDD, Mocha.

#### Productora de Software PSL, Bogotá, Colombia

Jun. 2018 – Aug. 2018

Frontend Developer

- Be part of an international Team to deliver solution to support a Product for end user
- Technologies/Languages: HTML, CSS, AngularJS
- SCRUM methodology

## **QRVEY, Barranguilla, Colombia**

May. 2017 - May. 2018

Frontend developer

- Worked for a U.S. client building a self-service platform.
- Technologies/Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AngularJS, Angular 4, Sourcetree, sketch, gulp, JIRA, bootstrap, media queries
- SCRUM Methodology
- Responsive design

## VSI/Novo Scale, Bogotá, Colombia

Technical consultant

- Worked on cloud platform **SERVICENOW** to bring solutions to different clients in the U.S.
- Technologies/Languages: JavaScript, Rhino
- SCRUM Methodology

# **OSF Global Services S.A.S, Bogotá, Colombia**

Dec. 2015 - Mar. 2016

Jun. 2016 - Sept. 2016

Frontend developer

- Worked with e-commerce platform **DEMANDWARE** to e-commerce site migration for a worldwide watches brand
- Technologies/Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Photoshop, sourcetree, bitbucket
- SCRUM methodology

# Bengala estudio S.A.S, Bogotá, Colombia

Feb. 2013 - Sept. 2015

Web developer

- Creation of web sites for many companies in Colombia (Landing pages and complete web sites) using CMS such eZPublish, Wordpress and Joomla
- Creation of Facebook apps using API
- Technologies/Languages: HMTL, CSS, sass, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery, PHP, MySQL, tortoise SVN

## Aplyca Tecnología S.A.S, Bogotá, Colombia

Apr. 2010 – Aug. 2012

Frontend developer

- Creation and support of web sites for clients in Colombia and U.S. that were built with eZPublish CMS
- Technologies/Languages: HMTL, CSS, sass, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery, tortoise SVN

#### Education

**Santo Tomas University**, Bogotá, Colombia BS, Electronic Engineering

Feb. 2001 - Dec. 2009